http://www.ixys.com/privacy.aspx

DistrStock
You are using an unlicensed and unsupported version of DotNetNuke Professional Edition. Please contact sales@dnncorp.com for information on how to obtain a valid license.
Privacy Statement
IXYS Website is committed to protecting your privacy and developing
technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This
Statement of Privacy applies to the IXYS Website Web
site and governs data collection and usage. By using the IXYS Website
website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
IXYS Website collects personally
identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work
address or telephone number. IXYS Website also collects anonymous
demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code,
age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and
software that is automatically collected by IXYS Website. This information
can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and
referring Web site addresses. This information is used by IXYS Website for
the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to
provide general statistics regarding use of the IXYS Website Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable
information or personally sensitive data through IXYS Website public
message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note:
IXYS Website does not read any of your private online communications.
IXYS Website encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites
you choose to link to from IXYS Website so that you can understand how
those Web sites collect, use and share your information. IXYS Website is
not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites
outside of the IXYS Website and IXYS Website family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
IXYS Website collects and uses your personal
information to operate the IXYS Website Web site and deliver the services
you have requested. IXYS Website also uses your personally identifiable
information to inform you of other products or services available from
IXYS Website and its affiliates. IXYS Website may also contact you
via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of
potential new services that may be offered.
IXYS Website does not sell,
rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. IXYS Website may, from
time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a
particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique
personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number)
is not transferred to the third party. In addition, IXYS Website may share
data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you
email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All
such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except
to provide these services to IXYS Website, and they are required to
maintain the confidentiality of your information.
IXYS Website does not
use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or
political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
IXYS Website keeps
track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within IXYS Website,
in order to determine what IXYS Website services are the most popular.
This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within
IXYS Website to customers whose behavior indicates that they are
interested in a particular subject area.
IXYS Website Web sites will
disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so
by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a)
conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on
IXYS Website or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of
IXYS Website; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the
personal safety of users of IXYS Website, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The IXYS Website Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your
online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by
a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to
your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a
web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary
purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The
purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a
specific page. For example, if you personalize IXYS Website pages, or
register with IXYS Website site or services, a cookie helps
IXYS Website to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.
This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as
billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same
IXYS Website Web site, the information you previously provided can be
retrieved, so you can easily use the IXYS Website features that you
customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web
browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser
setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you
may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the
IXYS Website services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
IXYS Website secures your personal information from
unauthorized access, use or disclosure. IXYS Website secures the
personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a
controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or
disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is
transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption,
such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
IXYS Website will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect
company and customer feedback. IXYS Website encourages you to periodically
review this Statement to be informed of how IXYS Website is protecting
your information.
Contact Information
IXYS Website welcomes your comments
regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that IXYS Website has
not adhered to this Statement, please contact IXYS Website at d.huynh@ixys.net. We
will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the
problem.
Home   |   Product Portfolio   |   Applications   |   Technical Support   |   IXYS Divisions   |   Corporate   |   Sales/Contacts
Copyright 2010 by DotNetNuke Corporation
Privacy Statement
Terms Of Use
